// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "Who developed Python Programming Language?",
      answer: "Guido van Rossum",
      options: [
        "Wick van Rossum",
        " Rasmus Lerdorf",
        " Guido van Rossum",
        " Niene Stom"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "Which type of Programming does Python support?",
      answer: "all of the mentioned",
      options: [
        "object-oriented programming",
        "structured programming",
        "functional programming",
        "all of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "Is Python case sensitive when dealing with identifiers?",
      answer: "no",
      options: [
        "no",
        "yes",
        "machine dependent",
        "none of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: " Which of the following is the correct extension of the Python file?",
      answer: ".py",
      options: [
        " .python",
        ".pl",
        ".py",
        ".p"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: " Is Python code compiled or interpreted?",
      answer: "Python code is neither compiled nor interpreted",
      options: [
        "Python code is both compiled and interpreted",
        "Python code is neither compiled nor interpreted",
        " Python code is only compiled",
        "Python code is only interpreted"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "All keywords in Python are in _________",
      answer: "None of the mentioned",
      options: [
        "Capitalized",
        "lower case",
        "UPPER CASE",
        "None of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "Which of the following is used to define a block of code in Python language?",
      answer: "Indentation",
      options: [
        "Indentation",
        "Key",
        "Brackets",
        "All of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "Which keyword is used for function in Python language?",
      answer: "Def",
      options: [
        "Function",
        " Def",
        " fun",
        "Define"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "Which of the following character is used to give single-line comments in Python?",
      answer: "!",
      options: [
        "//",
        " #",
        " !",
        " /*"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "What does pip stand for python?",
      answer: "Preferred Installer Program",
      options: [
        "unlimited length",
        "all private members must have leading and trailing underscores",
        "Preferred Installer Program",
        "none of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
  ];